Name:- Chunnu Kumar Contact:- +91 7269926729

E-Mail:- chunnukumar198@gmail.com

Address:- H.No-21A, Neelkanth Enclave, Sector-69, Badshah Pur Gurgaon (122101).

OBJECTIVE

To work in an organization which gives me a chance to develop my technical skills, this helps in progress of the organization as well as my personal development.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced software engineer with a passion for developing innovative programs that expedite the efficiency and effectiveness of organizational success. Well-versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly.

- Efficient in working with Angular.
- Working knowledge of Angular.
- Effective in working independently and collaboratively in teams.
- Always learn new technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

My Total Experience 5.5 Years as a software developer but I currently working on angular developer and 2.6 Years in angular Experience.

Feb 2018 - Jul 2018

Working as a **Angular Developer** at **Monet Networks**, Gurgaon, from **27 Jan 2021 to date**.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Technologies : Angular , HTML ,CSS , JavaScript ,TypeScript .

Servers : AWS.

Databases : MYSQL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Zoom HKG Infosoft Pvt.Ltd

Pocket 14, Sector-24, Rohini

New Delhi-110085

www.zoomhkg.com/

Software Developer Jul 2018 – Sep 2019

Virtual Mind Infotech

D-22 Sectot 3 Noida -110085

http://www.virtualmindinfotech.com/

Software Developer Sep 2019 – 22 Jan 2021

HD Network Media

B-448, Dwarka Sectot – 9

New Delhi -110075

Angular Developer

27 Jan 2021

Present Monet Network

https://www.monetanalytics.com/#/

Sohna Road, Gurugram Sectot – 69.

EDUCATION

Master Degree in computer applications (MCA). Kanpur Institute Of Technology (Kanpur).

Bachelor Degree in computer Application (BCA). R.L.S.Y College Aurangabad (Bihar)

STRENGTH

- Good communication and interpersonal skills.
- Ability to work in a team environment.
- Quick learner
- Ability to work under pressure.
- Adaptability
- Focused and Determined To prove myself

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth : 11th Feb 1994 **Languages Known** : Hindi, English

Father's Name : Shri. Vindeshwari Singh

Sex:MaleMarital Status:MarriedNationality:Indian

Strengths : Honesty, Optimistic, Hard-Working

Hobbies:Reading, MusicInterest:Computers, Learning

Games : Cricket.

Declaration: I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Date: Chunnu Kumar

Place: Gurugram